A Guide to the Studies of the Virginia Division of Legislative Services, 1978-2000.
Library of Virginia
- Studies (Accession 39745), 1978-1995., Extent: 12 cubic feet (12 boxes)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Other states, undated. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Other states, undated. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Public hearings, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Report, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Report summary, undated. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Resource list, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Tapes of hearings, 1992 July 30. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Virginia Code (existing), 1992. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Written testimony, 1992 July 8. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Written testimony, 1992 July 30. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Written testimony, 1992 Aug 4. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Chairman Reports, 1995. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Studies, 1992-1996. (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Studies (Accession 40083), 1987-1999., Extent: 22 cubic feet (22 boxes)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Procedural Aspects of the Trial, Appeal and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases (HJR 402) - Death Penalty, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Procedural Aspects of the Trial, Appeal and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases (HJR 402) - Agendas, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Procedural Aspects of the Trial, Appeal and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases (HJR 402) - Related material, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Procedural Aspects of the Trial, Appeal and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases (HJR 402) - Report, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Procedural Aspects of the Trial, Appeal and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases (HJR 402) - Studies of death penalty trials and appeals of capital cases, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Procedural Aspects of the Trial, Appeal and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases (HJR 402) - Death Penatly Subcommittee, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - General, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Agendas, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Reports, 1994-1995. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Working papers, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Other materials, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Related materials, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Preneed Funeral Contracts (HJR 141) - Meetings, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Lien Enforcement (SB 255 and SB 256) - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Reports, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Federal statistics, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Reports and articles, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Child Support Enforcement Cases, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Social Security Numbers, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 615) - Statistics, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 485) - Child Support Enforcement correspondence, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 485) - Statutes and cases, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 485) - Child support, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Post Majority Child Support and Occupational License Withholding for Failure to Pay Child Support (HJR 485) - Post majority reports and articles, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Special Subcommittee Studyting Landfill Gas Pipelines (HB 2471), 1995. (Box 2)
  - Subcommittee Studying Fireworks Legislation (HB 2553) -, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Minimum Levels of Motor Vehicle Liability and Property Insurance (HJR 601) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Minimum Levels of Motor Vehicle Liability and Property Insurance (HJR 601) - Agendas, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Minimum Levels of Motor Vehicle Liability and Property Insurance (HJR 601) - Related material, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Minimum Levels of Motor Vehicle Liability and Property Insurance (HJR 601) - Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Minimum Levels of Motor Vehicle Liability and Property Insurance (HJR 601) - Meetings and minutes, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meetings and Minutes, 1995. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Agendas, 1995. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meeting, 1995 Sept 22. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meeting, 1995 Oct 6. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meeting, 1995 Nov 13. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meeting, 1995 Dec 6. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meeting, 1995 Dec 12. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Meeting, 1996 Jan 11. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Related Materials, 1995. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying OB/GYN Services in Managed Care Plans (HJR 560) - Reports, 1996. (Box 3)
  - Oil Spill Response Capability / Oil Spill Readiness (HJR 265) - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act (HJR 701) - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act (HJR 701) - Related Material, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Funding Requirements of the Virginia Unemployment Compensation Act (SJR 234) - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Funding Requirements of the Virginia Unemployment Compensation Act (SJR 234) - Agendas, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Funding Requirements of the Virginia Unemployment Compensation Act (SJR 234) - Meetings and Minutes, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Funding Requirements of the Virginia Unemployment Compensation Act (SJR 234) - Related Material, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Funding Requirements of the Virginia Unemployment Compensation Act (SJR 234) - Reports, 1993-1994. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (HJR 524) - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (HJR 524) - Agendas, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (HJR 524) - Meetings and Minutes, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (HJR 524) - Reports, 1993-1994. (Box 3)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (HJR 524) - Related Material, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Battered Person Syndrome (Ad Hoc Study) (HB 959) - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Battered Person Syndrome (Ad Hoc Study) (HB 959) - Related Material, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Records Dissemination (Ad Hoc Study) (HB 478) - Comments on Draft, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 173) - Minutes, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 173) - Related Material, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 173) - Working Papers, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 173) - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 173) - Agendas, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 173) - Reports, 1992-1993. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 66) - Correspondence, 1988. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 66) - Reports, 1988. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 66) - Meetings and Minutes, 1988. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 305) - Correspondence, 1989. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Statutes of Limitation and Accrual of Action (HJR 305) - Meetings and Minutes, 1989. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission on Workers Compensation - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission Workers Compensation - Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1993-1994. (Box 4)
  - Study of the Impact of Third Party Reimbursement on the Commonwealth's Pharmacies (HJR 101) - Agendas, 1994. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Virginia Consumer Protection Act (HJR 143), 1994. (Box 4)
  - Uniform Commercial Code Study - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Commission on Violent Crime - Reports, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Sport Shooting Ranges (Ad Hoc Subcommittee Study) - Militia and Police Committee, 1994. (Box 4)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist Small Businesses (SJR 314) - Agendas, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist Small Businesses (SJR 314) - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist Small Businesses (SJR 314) - Meetings and Minutes, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist Small Businesses (SJR 314) - Related Materials, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist Small Businesses (SJR 314) - Reports, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist Small Businesses (SJR 314) - Testimony of Microenterprise and Enterprise Zones, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Court-appointed Counsel Fees (HJR 509) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Court-appointed Counsel Fees (HJR 509) - Related Materials, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Court-appointed Counsel Fees (HJR 509) - Resolutiona and Membership, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (SJR 339) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Proposed Modifications to the Uniform Commercial Code (SJR 339) - Resolution and Membership, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Computer Virus Study (Courts of Justice Committees) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Special Ad Hoc Committee of the House and Senated Courts of Justice Committees Studying Immunity Legislation - Records, 1995-1996. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Means of Encouraging Prompt and Equitable Resolution of Civil Disputes (Tort Cases) (SJR 385) - Agendas, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Means of Encouraging Prompt and Equitable Resolution of Civil Disputes (Tort Cases) (SJR 385) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Means of Encouraging Prompt and Equitable Resolution of Civil Disputes (Tort Cases) (SJR 385) - Related Materials, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Means of Encouraging Prompt and Equitable Resolution of Civil Disputes (Tort Cases) (SJR 385) - Reports, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Means of Encouraging Prompt and Equitable Resolution of Civil Disputes (Tort Cases) (SJR 385) - Resolution and Membership, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Development (HJR 236/1994 and HJR 593/1993) - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Development (HJR 236/1994 and HJR 593/1993) - Meeting, 1993-1994. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Development (HJR 236/1994 and HJR 593/1993) - Enterprise Zones, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Development (HJR 236/1994 and HJR 593/1993) - Weed and Seed Programs, 1993-1994. (Box 5)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Blighted and Deteriorated Housing in Virginia - Records, 1994. (Box 5)
  - Special Ad Hoc Committee Studyin DUI and Driving Without a License Violations, 1993. (Box 5)
  - Commission on Sentence and Parole Reforms (HJR 464) - Records, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Jail and Financing Mechanisms (HJR 574) - Records, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Circuit Court Clerk's Fees (HJR 790) - Agendas, 1993-1994. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Circuit Court Clerk's Fees (HJR 790) - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Circuit Court Clerk's Fees (HJR 790) - Meetings and Minutes, 1993-1994. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Circuit Court Clerk's Fees (HJR 790) - Reports, 1993-1994. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Juvenile Detention Homes / Secure Juvenil Detention (HJR 446) - Records, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Special Subcommittees Studying Workers' Compensation Insurance / Governor's Advisory Commission on Workers' Compensation (SB 412 / HB 1186) - Agendas, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - Special Subcommittees Studying Workers' Compensation Insurance / Governor's Advisory Commission on Workers' Compensation (SB 412 / HB 1186) - Meetings and Minutes, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - Special Subcommittees Studying Workers' Compensation Insurance / Governor's Advisory Commission on Workers' Compensation (SB 412 / HB 1186) - Related Materials, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - Special Subcommittees Studying Workers' Compensation Insurance / Governor's Advisory Commission on Workers' Compensation (SB 412 / HB 1186) - Reports, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - VASAP Advisory Board - Vehicle Ignition Interlock Systems Study - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 6)
  - VASAP Advisory Board - Vehicle Ignition Interlock Systems Study - Related Material, 1994. (Box 6)
  - Commission on the Reduction of Sexual Assaulth Victimization in Virginia (SJR 108) - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Commission on the Reduction of Sexual Assaulth Victimization in Virginia (SJR 108) - Related Materials, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Commission on the Reduction of Sexual Assault Victimization in Virginia (SJR 108) - Reports, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Habitual Sex Offenders (HJR 193) - Records, 1994. (Box 6)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Prevention of School Crime and Violence (HJR 213) - Records, 1994. (Box 7)
  - Ad Hoc Joint Subcommittee on School Crime and Violence (HJR 832), 1992-1993. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Corrections information, 1995. (Box 7)
  - VASAP Ad Hoc Committee on Use and Lose Statute - Records, 1994. (Box 7)
  - House Courts of Justice Special Subcommittee Studying HB 5004, Crime Victim and Witness Rights Act - Records, 1994-1995. (Box 7)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Witness Protection Programs - Records, 1994. (Box 7)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Witness Protection Programs - Survey of Witness Protection Programs, 1994. (Box 7)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 236) - Records, 1994-1995. (Box 7)
  - Theft of Vehicles from Dealerships - Records, 1996. (Box 7)
  - Virginia State Crime Commission - Study of the Feasibility of a Drug Court Pilot Program in Virginia - Records, 1993-1994. (Box 7)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia's Drug Laws (SJR 74/1996 and SJR 296/1995) - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 8)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia's Drug Laws (SJR 74/1996 and SJR 296/1995) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 8)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia's Drug Laws (SJR 74/1996 and SJR 296/1995) - Related Materials, 1995-1996. (Box 8)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia's Drug Laws (SJR 74/1996 and SJR 296/1995) - Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 8)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia's Drug Laws (SJR 74/1996 and SJR 296/1995), 199. (Box 8)
  - Governor's Commission on Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform - General, 1994. (Box 9)
  - Governor's Commission on Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform - Public Hearings (Alexandria, Fairfax, Fredericksburg, Norfolk, Richmond and Wytheville, 1994. (Box 9)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Agendas, 1996. (Box 10)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 10)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Meetings and minutes, 1996. (Box 10)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Related materials, 1996. (Box 10)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Reports, 1996. (Box 10)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Ad Hoc Subcommittee Studying Legislative Immunity and Judicial Ethics, 1996. (Box 10)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Bill drafting, 1996. (Box 11)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Related materials, 1996. (Box 11)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Reports, 1996. (Box 11)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Sovereign Immunity (HJR 33) - Related materials, 1996. (Box 12)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Coal Dust Emissions (SJR 27) - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Coal Dust Emissions (SJR 27) - Reports, 1993-1994. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 201) - Agendas, 1993-1994. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 201) - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 201) - Related materials, 1993-1994. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 201) - Reports, 1993-1994. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Measures to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 1) - Agendas, 1992. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Measures to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 1) - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Measures to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 1) - Minutes, 1992. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Measures to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 1) - Related materials, 1992. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Measures to Reduce Emissions from Coal-Carrying Railroad Cars (SJR 1) - Reports, 1992. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Use Incentives for Joint Activities by Localities (SJR 128), 1992. (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Mental Incapacity and Consent to Sexual Activity (HJR 80) - Correspondence, 1996-1997. (Box 14)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Mental Incapacity and Consent to Sexual Activity (HJR 80) - Related material, 1996-1997. (Box 14)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Mental Incapacity and Consent to Sexual Activity (HJR 80) - Reports, 1996-1997. (Box 14)
  - Ad Hoc Study of Youth Tobacco Use, 1996-1997. (Box 14)
  - Joint Ad Hoc Committee on Guardianship (SB 408), 1996-1997. (Box 14)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Science and Technology (HJR 195) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 14)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Science and Technology (HJR 195) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 14)
  - Computer Crimes (HB 1649), 1995. (Box 14)
  - Joint Subcommittee Study of Crime Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593), 1995. (Box 14)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593) - Agendas, 1993-1994. (Box 15)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593) - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 15)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593) - Meetings and minutes, 1993-1994. (Box 15)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593) - Related materials, 1993-1994. (Box 15)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593) - Safe Neighbors, 1993-1994. (Box 15)
  - Study of Crime and Violence Prevention Through Community Economic Stimulation and Development (HJR 593) - Weed and Seed, 1993-1994. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Stranded Costs and Related Issue Task Force meeting, 1998 May 26. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Stranded Costs and Related Issue Task Force meeting, 1998 June 30. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Stranded Costs and Related Issue Task Force meeting, 1998 July 30. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Stranded Costs and Related Issue Task Force meeting, 1998 Aug 21. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Stranded Costs and Related Issue Task Force meeting, 1998 Sept 18. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Meeting, 1998 May 7. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Meeting, 1998 June 3. (Box 16)
  - Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility Restructuring (SJR 91) - Meeting, 1998 July 9. (Box 16)